Why are you in such a hurry to leave?
Yeah.
That little brother
is quite nice.
And he's our fan.
He has a problem.
Don't you think
he was fishing for information just now?
If you don't believe me,
stay here later
and you'll see.
Fu Binyan.
Why are you still here?
I knew it was you.
How did you get in?
I just asked their captain
if I could come in.
And he said yes?
Maybe because
I help them with math.
Let's go.
Xie Yizhou should be coming in.
Pass the ball.
Good, cool.
Hurry up, hurry up.
Make up for it, make up for it.
Go, go, go.
Shoot.
Coach.
Here.
Get ready to go on the field later.
Group A, off the court.
Group C, get ready.
It's him.
Number 11.
It's really him.
I knew it.
He's amazing.
He's Xie Yizhou,
from the Middle School Affiliated to the Institute of Physical Education.
He's 14 years old.
Don't be fooled by his age
and shorter stature.
His strength
is the most dazzling
in the whole team.
Are you okay?
I seem to have seen him somewhere,
but I can't remember.
Cool.
Those guys
seem to be here again.
Should we go and drive them away?
It's okay. They are my friends.
Let them see for a while.
After all, the next time we meet
will be on the court.
Xie Yizhou
is so scary.
He plays well,
and he is so cunning.
Shame.
So embarrassing.
I can't believe
I was fooled
by a 14-year-old kid.
Don't be nervous.
If I wanted to expose you,
I wouldn't have helped you
just now.
He's not only skilled,
but also good at psychology.
He knows how to mislead the enemy
and how to extract information.
Senior Li Haoyu
is good at quick breakthroughs.
Senior Lin Qingyuan
has a high shooting accuracy.
He trains every day.
What do you think?
You're right.
Our new plan
is not enough.
Why?
Xie Yizhou has a good defensive awareness.
He was constantly
monitoring his teammates' positions
and predicting the ball's trajectory.
If
we just spread out
our attack,
he'll quickly
penetrate our defense.
What should we do?
You need to find someone
with similar skills.
Gu Chenyang is a good choice.
His consciousness and speed
are similar to his.
Yes.
I also think we are similar.
But I always feel
he seems to know me.
Know you?
I can't explain it.
It's just a feeling.
I have to go back.
It's so early.
My dad and I
have a weekly meeting
every Friday at 7.
I'll discuss
Xie Yizhou's situation
with Coach Su later.
You guys think of something too,
especially you,
Fu Binyan.
Help us out.
Do you think Gu Chenyang
has a similar work style
to your mom?
No, not really.
Why not?
My mom is a classic workaholic,
the more she works, the more energized she gets.
But Gu Chenyang,
he doesn't seem like that.
Really?
I thought he was born to be
a master of planning.
No, no, no.
He was as undisciplined as me
when he was a child.
Now he's really becoming
more and more like his father.
I'm still here
wasting time with you.
I'm leaving.
Wait.
Please.
We need you.
Yeah.
Gu Chenyang said
especially you.
Please help us.
You told me to ask for help
when I need it.
So
please help us
to give us some advice.
Fine.
I can think of a way,
but you have to balance your studies.
In this monthly quiz,
I'm still the top in the grade,
but my total score
has dropped compared to before.
The main problem
is the last question
of math
and the English listening.
The reason for the decline in math
is that I didn't fully understand
the knowledge points of the new unit.
So from now on,
I will do an extra set of questions every day
to reinforce and consolidate.
The English listening
was due to a lack of careful reading of the questions.
In the future, I will also strengthen
my practice of English listening.
Losing ten points in total
is a very serious mistake.
Right?
Should it be taken as a lesson?
I will, Dad.
Next,
it's the monthly reading report.
This month, our school has launched
a reading week event.
I will read more books
from the school's reading list.
This month, I read
The Catcher in the Rye
and Fu Lei's Family Letters.
The reading report
has been sent to your email.
I've seen it.
It's well written.
How's your tennis practice going?
I'm still practicing tennis according to the plan.
You must keep it up.
If you're considering
studying abroad,
tennis can be a big plus.
Okay?
Of course, that's one thing.
Another is
it shows your determination.
Dad,
actually, I think
domestic academic planning
might be more suitable for me.
I have a meeting.
Let's discuss it
when I return to China, okay?
See you next week.
I'm looking forward to your good news.
You passed the exam.
[Congratulations to our students]
[on winning awards]
[in the provincial high school students']
[mathematical Olympiad.]
Fu Binyan and Zhou Yang.
Who won the prize?
Zhou Yang and Fu Binyan in Grade 11.
They are amazing.
Not only that,
they cooperate with each other.
How enviable!
It's been a long time
since I've had the feeling of
winning together.
It's a pity
that it's not on the basketball court.
But it's already
very good now.
Pleasure working with you.
Fu Binyan.
Training is over.
Why don't you go back?
I want to tell you something.
What is it?
I know your secret.
What secret?
When you play basketball,
you often smile.
You don't even know it yourself, do you?
That's all?
I've been watching you for a long time.
You usually have a cold face,
and everyone is a bit afraid of you.
But as long as you face basketball,
like this,
you really love basketball.
You should pay more attention
to your skills.
Delete the photos.
You're all talk,
but my camera
never lies.
Stop, stop!
Li Haoyu,
what was that
defense?
Are you playing games?
Coach, I just want to intercept the ball.
To intercept the ball, you need to stay calm.
Don't be like an old lady
fighting for eggs in the supermarket.
I'm adding extra practice for you tonight
for the next game.
Your cooperation
is crucial.
Whether it's offense or defense,
you both need to step up.
Understand?
Yes, sir.
One more time.
Watch out!
Are you okay?
Where are you hurt?
My wrist.
Don't move.
Let me see.
Coach.
It hurts.
Let's go to the hospital.
OK.
Have some water.
I'm sorry
for today.
I was careless
and hurt you.
It's okay.
I'll be fine in a couple of days.
Don't move around.
Your hand's hurt.
Let me help you.
Stop pushing yourself.
The doctor said you need to rest.
How can I rest?
Coach Su just said
we need to
step up for the next game.
Now my right hand's injured.
I need to come up with a new plan.
Stop right there.
Gu Chenyang,
just
take a break.
But without a new plan,
I can't relax.
If you don't rest now,
we won't be able to relax either.
Drink some water, drink some water.
Chenyang, you're injured?
Is it serious?
Auntie, you're finally back.
Gu Chenyang's hand is swollen,
and he's still working with it injured.
Please tell him to take a break.
Thank you, Haoyu.
I'll be on my way then.
Gu Chenyang, take care of your hand.
Don't move it around.
Don't take the tablet away.
Let me see.
Does it hurt?
Mom, I'm fine.
It's normal playing basketball.
How could you be so careless?
You still say you're fine.
I'm so worried about you.
Mom,
I'll be more careful next time.
What do you want for dinner?
I'll cook for you.
You need
something light
to help your body recover.
How about I make you some soup?
Rib soup, maybe?
You
shouldn't do anything for the next few days.
Just rest up.
Have a glass of milk.
Thank you, mom.
Still studying hard, huh?
What's up, mom?
Tell me,
how much you love playing basketball.
Mom.
You used to say
that whatever I do
is like fulfilling
my dad's expectations,
only focusing on efficiency and results.
But basketball is different.
It's truly special.
Just like you said,
like real reading.
I can feel
every breath and heartbeat,
every move and shot
on the court.
Every minute,
I'm happy.
Really happy.
I see.
I understand.
But
your dad sent me
a message today.
His exchange program
has ended early.
He'll be back this weekend.
Since you like it so much,
talk to him about it when he gets back.
I'll prepare well
for every game from now on
and prove it to him with results.
I'm not talking about grades.
I mean expressing your love.
Tell him your feelings.
Mom,
do you support me in playing basketball?
Of course.
As long as you're happy,
even if you just
run around on the court
all your life,
I'll be happy for you.
No.
My son should be
a rising star
on the track.
But
I can understand your dad.
After all, he's been there.
He's asking you to do this
for your future.
Don't be discouraged.
Cheer up.
You still have me.
As long as you need,
I will always be by your side.
I will support you unconditionally
and your love.
Mom.
Thank you.
Okay, I won't bother you anymore.
Drink the milk and go to bed early.
Okay.
Good night.
Good night, mom.
Should I
play a good game,
or have a good talk
with him?
Team data analysis.
Didn't you
quit the basketball team?
The team captain
got injured tonight,
so I'm helping out with the analysis.
This level of detail
isn't something
you can do
on a whim.
Trying to fool me?
You're still too young.
Yan,
I don't like beating around the bush.
I have to tell you,
I don't approve of you playing basketball again.
I know.
But
I fully support you
in your love for basketball.
Have you ever considered
finding another way
to return to the court?
Another way?
A data analyst
Playing basketball on the court
is not the only way
to show your love for basketball.
You're good at
data analysis.
You can return to the team
in this way,
and give full play to your strengths.
What do you think?
If you don't like it, just forget it.
If you like it, just do it.
The worst thing is to be hesitant
and not do what you say.
That's not me.
Fu Yuqing's son.
Coach Su
I have something to talk to you.
What's wrong?
Come on.
Start your show.
I've decided
to join the basketball club
as a data analyst.
I've already talked to
Director Qian.
Fu Binyan has officially
become one of us.
Don't you agree?
Agree!
We've been waiting for you for a long time.
But
why are you just an analyst
as MVP?
What a waste!
Yeah.
It's better to play basketball.
Yeah, let's play together.
You lead us to victory.
Analysts are also important.
What are you talking about?
Okay.
Fu Binyan as the analyst
can help Coach Su enrich the tactics,
and also help Gu Chenyang share the pressure.
It's the best return.
Well summarized.
Alright, since you're here,
the analyst should get ready.
Observe everyone's condition,
and get familiar with it.
Come on, change clothes.
Okay.
Welcome.
You know about him too?
What about him?
I thought I was the only one who knew.
It's putting a lot of pressure on me.
We didn't give anything away, did we?
It was a bit forced,
but it should be fine.
That's good.
Now that we're on the same page,
let's work together from now on.
Or
let's make up an excuse first.
He has officially joined us.
It's inevitable that
he'll be asked to perform again.
It's better to be prepared in advance.
Precaution is better than cure.
It makes sense.
What excuse should we make up?
Let me help you.
You two are talking so loudly
that the whole school can hear you.
But thank you anyway.
I'll figure out a way to deal with
this kind of situation by myself.
Fu Binyan
You suddenly decided to join the Basketball Club.
Is it because my right hand is injured?
Don't get me wrong.
I just
want to join it.
I hope you won't make me regret.
You're still so proud.